Toggle navigation

[Home](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/) | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

– Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
– We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
– We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
– We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
– Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
– We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
– We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Search

Or, Select Month July 2023  (1) January 2023  (1) June 2022  (1) April 2022  (1) April 2021  (1) December 2020  (1) November 2020  (2) October 2020  (1) September 2020  (1) March 2020  (1) December 2019  (2) June 2019  (1) May 2019  (1) December 2018  (2) September 2018  (2) August 2018  (1) June 2018  (1) April 2018  (3) March 2018  (3) February 2018  (5) January 2018  (3) December 2017  (7) November 2017  (3) October 2017  (1) September 2017  (1) August 2017  (2) July 2017  (2) June 2017  (3) November 2016  (1) August 2016  (1)

Related Links

* \> [MG Discord](https://discord.gg/mcleodgaming)
* \> [MG YouTube Channel](https://www.youtube.com/McLeodGaming)
* \> [GregMcLeod.com](http://www.gregmcleod.com/)
* \> [Contact Us](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/contact)

  Donate

Sponsored

Copyright © 2003-2024, McLeodGaming Inc. All Rights Reserved.

[View Credits](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/credits) - [Cookie Policy](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/cookie-policy) - [Privacy](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/privacy-policy)

This site uses cookies: [Find out more.](https://www.mcleodgaming.com/cookie-policy)Okay, thanks
